jobsinme.com 2019-01-08

# Privacy Policy | Jobs In ME

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared. JobsInTheUS.com has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the online, website and/or mobile platform products related to the JobsInTheUS.com network of sites (the "Products"). We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. 

Cookies

We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a web server to store on a web browser so it can later be read back from that browser. This is useful for having the browser remember specific information so that your experience is customized. This allows us to store preferences of start pages.

Registration Forms

Our registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as their name, email, and postal address). Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with our users when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Email addresses

An email address is required to register. JobsInTheUS.com will never sell or share your email address to a third party vendor without your permission. However, if you choose to publish your email address in a job or in a resume stored in our database, or accessible from our Products, this information becomes public, and there is a possibility this information can then be copied by visitors to our Products.

Content And Access

If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses. We may also retain any messages you send through the Products. You may provide us information in user content you post to the Products.

When you download and use our Products, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier.

We collect your location based information for the purpose of setting up your phone and search preferences. We will not share this information with any third party. If you no longer wish to allow us to track your geo-location information in the mobile application you may turn this off at the device level.

Log File Information

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use the Products, our servers automatically records certain log file information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

Mobile Analytics

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within the mobile application.

External Links

The Products contain links to other websites managed by third parties. JobsInTheUS.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites.

Internal Review

JobsInTheUS.com may use certain information about you and/or your user content internally for purposes such as analyzing how the Products are used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing content.

We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our Products; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our Users or engineers that are associated with certain IP addresses; (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; and (g) automatically update the JobsInTheUS.com application on your devices.

Security

Our Products have security measures in place designed to seek to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control, which includes the creation of unique user Id's and passwords. However, we are not responsible if any third party evades our security procedures and gains access to your file and your contact information in violation of our rules and security measures. You must also be aware of the possibility that your resume and file information will be copied into hiring authority and recruiter databases. JobsInTheUS.com has no control over, nor will assume any liability for, the actions of any third parties in these contexts.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain JobsInTheUS.com services.

JobsInTheUS.com may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Products. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on JobsInTheUS.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. JobsInTheUS.com does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks JobsInTheUS.com to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. In addition, third-party advertisers may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices. The JobsInTheUS.com Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information.
